One such stock is neither falling on its own nor allowing
anyone else in its sector to fall, that is
ICICI Lode. Varun is ready to tell that
brother, tell me what happened with insurance, Anil
ji, insurance, I wish it was the case with the market too,
falling market is hedging,
market does not close, right, right, right, right, these days
even Saturdays have started opening, that's
right, and how many insurance companies should open,
Anil ji, if the market is like this, then there is no need to work on Saturday, do
n't do it, if the market is like this, even if it is for
three more days, that's good, very
good, so Anil ji, the results of the company have come out
and are much better than the expectations, in fact, when the data of
general insurance companies was coming out,
we had seen that there was a continuous
increase in the premium income
and in the results of the company, the
premium income has also increased to 13.5, not
only this, the claim ratio is
continuously decreasing, it has remained flat this time and there has been a
decrease in the expense ratio, so
obviously, if your
claim ratio, expense ratio, all these things go down, then it has a
direct impact on the company.  It
happens on profits and that is what we saw where an
increase of around 22 was seen. The
company had set a target of 102 for the combined ratio of 25
here and the
company is running around that. If you look at the return on average equity, then
this too has seen an
increase in this quarter. It has increased from 14.3 to
15.3. So if
you look at all the ratios, all of them
are indicating that you can see good growth in the company in the future. The
growth of the company in this quarter has been quite good. The
management is also very confident about the future growth. Not
only this,
brokerage houses are also confident about the growth of this company.
For this,
be it Goldman or CLS, both have increased their targets.
Goldman has increased it from 1475 to
1500, CLSA has increased it from 1620 to
around 1650. So this quarter, in
fact, if you look at the entire 9 months 5 24,
that too has been good and till now  The
trends that are coming
regarding the growth of these companies are also good and
for this you are seeing that after the results there
is a good jump in the stock of this company, there has been a
big action after the results and
because of this
you are seeing a good rise in the entire insurance space, IC
Lombard is still
seen holding its gains, so good action is being
created here.